agfg.com.au 2007-12-31

# Australian Good Food and Accommodation Guide Privacy

The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide periodically reviews its Privacy Policy and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide considers the responsible use of personal information to be of vital importance. The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide is committed to ensuring that to the best of our ability we meet all the requirements of the National Privacy Principals and the Privacy Act.

In general, you can visit the Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide website without revealing any personal information about yourself. However there are times when information will be collected, such as when you register for competitions or memberships, for billing purposes, appraisals or in connection with community postings such as message boards or feedback to us or to receive information from us. This information may include your name, home or business address and e-mail address. Personal information will only be collected when knowingly and voluntarily submitted.

The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide may share the information obtained with other organisations with a similar purpose to our own. We will endeavour to limit the use of the information to the purpose for which it was provided.

The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide will seek your permission to send you further communications at the time you provide us with your personal information. If at any time after submitting your personal information to The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide you would no longer like to receive information from us, simply follow the ‘unsubscribe’ directions at the end of any e-mail communications you receive.

No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect server logs. The statistics and log files may be preserved indefinitely and used at any time and in any way necessary to prevent security breaches and to ensure the integrity of the information supplied by The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide.

In general on The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide websites, IP addresses (a number that is unique to the computer through which you are connected to the internet) are logged to track a user's session while the user remains anonymous. We analyse this data for certain trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. In general, we do not link your IP addresses to anything personally identifiable to you. In those limited cases where session information is not anonymous, The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide will provide notice of the practice and an opportunity to 'opt out.'

When The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide receives information about your session or about you, we may also use it for research or to improve our site and the services we offer you.

## Cookies

Some The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide web pages use "cookies".

Cookies can make your subsequent visits to the web page simpler and more seamless. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (However, by not accepting cookies, some web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.). A server cannot find out a name or e-mail address, or anything about a user's computer, by using cookies. Cookie information is not stored or collected by The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide.

Once The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide receives information from you via e-mail or any other means, the information is in a secure environment. Your personal information will not be released unless The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide believes in good faith that the law requires it or your permission is granted.

## Security

The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and periodically updates its security measures in light of current technologies. You need to be aware of inherent risks associated with the transmission of information via the Internet. The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any personal information you submit to our sites. If you have concerns in this regard, The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide has other ways of obtaining and providing information. Normal mail, telephone and fax facilities are available.

The Australian Good Food & Accommodation Guide Websites may contain advertisements and links to other websites operated by third parties. These links are meant for your convenience only. We are not responsible for the privacy policies o these third party materials. Visitors to those sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices before disclosing personal information.
